Guide to the Leonid Tsypkin Papers M2209
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 7. Photographs
  - Other photographs [photos] (Box 9, Folder 4)
    All other photographs found with the archive and not belonging to any one specific file or collection. Includes the photo of 'peasant women' originally found among Tsypkin's manuscripts.
  - Microfilms (Boxes 10-11)
- Series 8. Audio Materials
  - Cassette tape with Leonid Tsypkin's voice (Box 9, Folder 1)
    The original recording is the sounds of Mikhail Tsypkin's childhood friends in Minsk performing musical pieces for him in 1962. In late 1981 or early 1982, Leonid Tsypkin re-record this tape to send to Mikhail in America and included some personal words over top it.
    This is the only known recording of Leonid Tsypkin's voice.